https://www.jcf.org/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
The Joseph Campbell Foundation (the JCF) is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the jcf.org site (the “Site”) hosted for JCF by Siteground Web Hosting; it does not apply to other online or offline JCF products or services. By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.
Collecting Your Personal Information
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, email address, company name, phone number, and region. The Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used for the operation and improvement of the Site.
Use of Your Personal Information
The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized.
In support of these uses, the JCF may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related JCF products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests.
We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other JCF products and services, and/or share information with JCF partners so they may send you information about their products and services.
The JCF occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as Web site hosting, packaging, mailing and delivering prizes, answering customer questions about products and services, and sending information about our products, special offers, and other new services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
The JCF may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the JCF or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of the JCF and our family of web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of JCF employees or agents, users of JCF products or services, or members of the public.
Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which the JCF or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. The JCF abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Control of Your Personal Information
Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of the JCF and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.
Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to the JCF in the context of other, separately operated, JCF products or services.
Security of Your Personal Information
The JCF is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Cookies
We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site’s features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other web sites you visit.
Changes to This Privacy Statement
We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the bottom of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
Contact Information
The JCF welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that the JCF has not adhered to this privacy statement, please contact us by e-mail or via postal mail at the address provided below, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Joseph Campbell Foundation
P.O.Box 1836
New York, NY 10026
United States of America
Last updated: 6/6/2018
Share this:Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on Reddit (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window)
Home
